So you know how I keep amplifying what I believe to be the reality in that the United States and
Zionist Israel are forming an even deeper alliance than the already deeper than the streets one they
already have. And that there are so many black people throughout the United States and the
Caribbean who will look at this and say, well, I mean, that's not really our problem. Hey,
I want you to take a grand look at this, the newest fashion in the Israeli government.
That's a noose pin. They're all wearing them. That right there, that's Itamar Ben-Gavir. He's the
minister of national security, rocking his noose pin proudly. Folks like Hakeem Jeffries, folks like
Cory Booker, folks like Bakari Sellers, folks like Hillary Clinton, folks like Barack Obama, folks like
Joe Biden, folks like Kamala Harris, all support these folks who are rocking this noose pin and you
think it's not going to come to you. So it's going to come down to, well, I'll let them do that as long
as they don't do it to me. And let me know how that feels for you. Houston, New Orleans, Dallas,
Atlanta, my What Would the Ancestors Say mission-driven book tour is coming your way. Come
on out, be in community, buy a book and get it signed. RSVP at amandaseals.com.
Thank you.